嘿  乔伊
Oh, hey, Joey.
-嘿  -我有点事要跟你商量
- Hey. - Listen, I need to ask you something.
你还记得我继父在监狱里的事吧
You know how my stepdad's in prison?
-嗯  -嗯
- Yeah. - Yeah.
这个周末他本来有个假期的
He was supposed to get a weekend furlough
这样明天他就能来参加我的婚礼了
so he could go to the wedding.
但是他刚刚打电话来说
But he just called and....
他在操场上捅了一个送冰的家伙
Well, apparently stabbing lceman in the exercise yard
他就不能忍到礼拜一吗
couldn't wait till Monday.
-这么说他来不了了吗   -对
- So he can't come? - No.
这么一来就没人
And so there's no one
挽着我走过红地毯了
to walk me down the aisle.
所以  嗯...
And....
我很希望你能挽着我
Well, I would just really love it if you would do it.
-真的   -对
- Seriously? - Yeah.
一直以来我都把你当作父亲一样
You've, you know, sort of been like a dad to me.
我是说  你一直以来都很照顾我
I mean, you've always, you know,
和我一起分享你的智慧
looked out for me and shared your wisdom.
我的确很有智慧
I am pretty "wisdomous."
所以...你觉得呢
So, what do you say?
当然  这是我的荣幸  菲比
Are you kidding? Phoebe, I would be honored.
哦  谢啦
Oh, thank you.
我希望
I hope....
你能够了解你对我来说有多么重要
I hope you know how much you mean to me.
听着  我希望
Listen, I hope....
我希望你知道...
I hope that you know....
我不想让你看到爸爸哭的样子
I don't want you to see your father cry.
回自己的房间去
Go to your room!
不不不  让你爸付吧
Oh, no, no, no. Let your dad get this.
是我的婚礼策划人
It's my wedding planner.
她快把我逼疯了
She's driving me crazy!
喂  行了  别这么大声嚷嚷
Hello? Okay, stop screaming!
好  那就比目鱼好了
Okay, so halibut.
好吧  三文鱼也行
All right, so salmon.
随便什么都好  我不...
Either way. I don't--
我无所谓
It doesn't matter to me.
可我有所谓
Well, it matters to me!
好吧  我不在乎  听你的好了
Well, I don't care. So you pick.
你刚才挂我的电话来着
Did you just hang up on me?
好了  听着
All right, look,
我要你在晚上十八点整的时候
I need you at the rehearsal dinner
准时到达婚礼彩排的现场
tonight at 1800 hours.
好  那是几点钟啊
Okay. What time is that?
你不知道军用时间
You don't know military time?
当时我肯定在接受导弹训练
I must have been in missile training the day
所以没学到
they taught that.
减12就行了
Just subtract 12.
好   那1800减去12
Okay, so 1800 minus 12...
就是1788
...is 1788.
-6点钟   -好的
- Six o'clock! - Okay.
等一下  好  我是盖勒
Hold on. Yeah? Geller here.
不  我说过了  一定要在4点之前送到
No, I said it has to be there by 4:00.
再见
Goodbye.
天呐  做一个冰雕有那么难么
God. How hard is it to make an ice sculpture?
等等  冰雕   太隆重了吧
Wait. Ice sculpture? That sounds really fancy.
我跟你说过我只想要一个简单的婚礼就好
I told you, I just want a simple wedding.
放心好了  亲爱的
Please, honey,
细节的东西都包在我身上
leave the details to me.
为了你  我会尽量把
Now, I wanna make this day
这一天弄得特别一些
as special for you as I can.
好了, 我打算让港湾乐队
I was thinking the harpist
穿成白色
should wear white.
港湾乐队
Harpist?
不是我朋友马乔里来敲钢鼓的吗
My friend Marjorie is playing the steel drums.
哦  她退出了
Oh, she backed out.
她退出了  为什么
She did? Why?
我叫她这么做的
I made her.
钢鼓和高雅的婚礼不太搭调
Steel drums don't really say "elegant wedding."
而且马乔里的体味太浓了
Nor does Marjorie's overwhelming scent.
嘿
Hey!
西藏独立之后她会洗澡的
She will shower when Tibet is free.
-嘿  你看起来真美   -你也是
- Hey. You look great. - You too.
我真高兴能有这么一次彩排
I'm glad we're having a rehearsal dinner.
我很少会在把这些食物吃下去之前
I rarely practice my meals
好好跟它们演习一下
before I eat.
还记得你答应过要送给我们的礼物是什么吗
What did we say was your one gift to us?
不开无聊的玩笑
No stupid jokes,
我以为那只是在正式的婚礼上
but I thought that was for the actual wedding.
先演习一下吧
Rehearse it.
嗨
Hi.
真高兴你们都来了
Thanks for coming, you guys.
哦  我...
Oh, yeah--
我只打算握个手
I was.... I was going for a handshake.
所以你把手顶在我的裤裆上
That why your hand's against my crotch?
-没错   -好了
- That is why. - Yeah.
瑞秋  艾玛呢
So, Rach, where's Emma?
莫妮卡让我把她送到我妈那里去了
Monica made me send her to my mom's.
显然  婴儿和婚礼可掺合不到一块儿
Apparently, babies and weddings don't mix.
你还在为你那烦人的小家伙哭哭啼啼的
Are you still crying about your damn baby?
菲比  待会儿致酒时你要说快点
Pheebs, you got to keep the line moving.
记住  跟每个人都是20秒
Remember, 20 seconds per person.
你和这些家伙天天见面
You see these clowns all the time.
嘿  你们是迈克的父母吧
Hey, you're Mike's parents, right?
是的
Yes, we are.
眼看着我们的小家伙们
Our little ones are
都长这么大了  是吧
growing up fast, aren't they?
-你说什么   -你知道
- How's that? - You know...
我们做父母的  一方面替他们感到高兴
...on one hand, you're happy for them.
但另一方面  又难免舍不得让他们离开
On the other, it's hard to let go.
你到底是谁啊
Who in God's name are you?
我也不喜欢你们  知道吗
I'm not that fond of you either, buddy.
我是看在孩子们的面子上才跟你们客气的
I'm just trying to be nice for the kids.
你知道我刚想起什么吗
You know what I realized?
咱俩还没有被分配在婚礼上的任务呢
We have no idea what we're doing in the wedding tomorrow.
对啊  我觉得咱们会是伴郎
Yeah, I thought we'd be groomsmen.
但都到这会儿了  他们怎么还不跟咱俩说呢
They would have asked us by now.
他们什么时候通知你做伴娘的
When did they ask you to be a bridesmaid?
呃... 11月
November.
我觉得情况有点不妙
I wanna say it's not looking good.
-嘿  菲比   -干吗
- Hey, Pheebs? - Sorry?
你还没有告诉他们俩
You haven't told these guys
在婚礼上要做什么呢
what they're doing in the wedding yet.
那个  他们不会出现在婚礼仪式上
Well, they're not in the wedding.
什么
What?
呃...
Well...
气氛有点尴尬
...this is really awkward.
哦  我可以走的
Oh, and I can leave.
真对不起你们
I'm sorry, you guys.
但迈克有一个弟弟
But Mike's got his brother
而且还有他在学校的死党
and his friends from school.
所以  你们...
So, you know, you were....
如果这么说能让你们好受一点
If it helps,
你们两个是头号候补
you were next in line.
就差那么一点
You just missed the cut.
天呐
Oh, man.
以前在选花样滑冰队员的时候就是这样
This is like figure skating team all over again.
我是说  花样游泳
I mean, synchronized swimming.
我的意思是  平衡木
I mean-- I mean, the balance beam.
-帮帮忙  -橄榄球
- Help me. - Football.
谢了
Thank you.
菲比  赶快吐出来  那里面有猪肉
Oh, Pheebs, spit that out. That has pork in it.
我记得那个砂锅应该是全素的
I thought the pot stickers were supposed to be vegetarian?
是的  但我做了点变动
Yeah, I changed them.
我发传真告诉你了
I sent you a fax about it.
可是我根本没有传真机啊
I don't have a fax machine.
那你可能会发现有一些意外
Well, then there are gonna be a few surprises.
我简直不敢相信
I can't believe we're gonna be
只有我们俩个不会出现在仪式上
the only people that aren't in this wedding.
是啊  我讨厌被冷落
I know. I hate being left out of things.
要知道这是一个婚礼
And it's a wedding.
如果缺了我感觉会很奇怪的
It'll be weird if I'm not in it.
-嘿  你们俩好吗   -还好啦
- Hey, guys, how's it going? - Fine.
这不  我们正坐着呢  就我们俩  无所事事
We're sitting here, alone, doing nothing.
我们在为明天做彩排呢
It's our rehearsal for tomorrow.
关于明天  我有个问题问你们
Look, about tomorrow, I've got a question for you.
我刚知道我的一个伴郎出了点急事
I found out one of my groomsmen had an emergency
所以不能来了
and can't make it.
出什么事了
What happened?
管他呢   所以...
Who cares? And...?
所以我在想  也许你们两个人中的一个能...
And I was wondering if one of you guys--
-我来替他   -不...  我...
- I'll do it! -No... Me!
你们两个都想做
You both wanna do it?
呃  只有一个名额
There's only room for one.
选我   我穿礼服可好看了
Pick me. I look great in a tux,
而且我也不会抢你的镜头
and I won't steal focus.
不  迈克
No, Mike.
不  选我  我的意思是  瞧...
No, no, you wanna pick me. I mean.... Watch.
我不太习惯
You know, I really don't feel very comfortable
来做这种决定
making this decision.
菲比更了解你们
You know, Phoebe knows you better.
我会让她来选
I'm gonna let her choose.
如果是菲比来选的话
Well, if Phoebe's choosing,
你现在就可以跟迈克的新伴郎打招呼了
then say hello to Mike's next groomsman.
哦  我会的  但我要先找一面镜子
Oh, I will. But I will need a mirror...
因为这个人就是我
...as he is me.
省省吧  你逊死了
Please. You're going down.
你更逊.
You are going "downer."
他们在选花样滑冰队员的时候就是这么说你的
They say that on the figure skating team?
我不知道  我没被选上
I wouldn't know. I didn't make it.
明天我会扮演菲比的继父
You know I'm filling in for Phoebe's stepdad tomorrow,
你知道吧
right?
知道  很感谢你能这么做
Yeah. Yeah. Hey, thanks for doing that.
哦  嘿  这是我的荣幸
Oh, hey, my pleasure.
那你对我的菲比有什么企图
So, what are your intentions with my Phoebe?
-我"企图"跟她结婚   -哦  还是个万金油
- I intend to marry her. - Oh, a wiseacre.
照我的理解
I understand you plan to support your wife
你似乎打算靠弹钢琴来养活老婆
by playing the piano?
这种工作好像不太稳定
Isn't that kind of unstable?
-跟演戏比起来还算好啦   -第二拳
- No more so than acting. - Strike two.
你说得对  我可能需要她来养活
You're right. She probably will support me.
嘿  除非我们搬去跟你一起住  爸爸
Hey, unless we move in with you, Dad.
第三拳
Strike three.
你只有最后一次机会了  迈克
You only get one more, Mike.
怎么样   你决定了没有
So? What did you decide?
我决定...要去厕所
I decided to pee.
他没告诉你吗
He didn't tell you?
你要在我们两个人里选一个
You have to choose one of us
来参加仪式
to be in your wedding.
有个伴郎来不了了
One of the groomsmen fell out.
哦, 不
Oh, no, no.
你们两个叫我怎么选啊
I can't choose between you two.
你们对我来说同样重要
I love you both so much.
的确重要
Just not enough to put us in
差一点就能参加原定的婚礼了
the original wedding party.
我没法选  这太...
But I don't wanna choose. It's....
哦  等一下  瑞秋
Okay, wait. Rach?
听着  我要给你一个很特别的伴娘任务
Listen, I have a very special bridesmaid task for you to do.
太棒了   选什么
Goody! What is it?
现在伴郎有一个空缺
Well, there's a spot open for only one groomsman...
你需要在罗斯和钱德勒中间选一个
...and you have to choose between Ross and Chandler.
所以...祝你好运
So good luck with that.
什么  什么
What? What, what, what?
不  不要  我不想选这个
No, I don't wanna do that.
好吧  看来我得去找个新的伴娘了
All right. I guess I have to find a new bridesmaid.
我来
I'll do it!
好了  现在是21点整
Okay, it's 2100 hours.
到你致辞的时间了
Time for your toast.
我能不能先去一下洗手间
Do I have time to go to the bathroom?
你的小便时间是20:30
You had a bathroom break at 2030.
要专时专用  迈克
Pee on your own time, Mike.
关于致酒词
In regards to the toasts, okay,
要尽量简短一些
you wanna keep them short.
婚礼彩排的时候
Nothing kills a rehearsal dinner
没有什么比又臭又长的致酒词更烦人了
like long speeches. Okay.
你要做的就是  上场  干活  然后走人
You just get in, do your thing, and get out.
你跟钱德勒也这么说
Is that what you say to Chandler?
现在已经21:01了
It's 2101,
我没心情跟你开玩笑
and I am not amused.
好吧
Okay.
新郎和新娘要说两句
The bride and groom have a few words they'd like to say.
嗨  大家好
Okay. Hello, everyone.
很高兴各位今晚能够光临
And thank you all for being here tonight.
明天就是正式的婚礼了
So tomorrow's the big event.
大家可能还不知道
Some of you might not know,
我和迈克的开始并不精彩
but Mike and I didn't get off to the best start.
是这样的  当时乔伊和我...
Yeah. My friend Joey and l...
决定相互替对方介绍朋友
...decided to fix each other up with friends. So l--
所以呢  我...
Oh, okay. I....
我... 我当时仔细考虑了半天
I gave it a lot of thought,
然后决定把我的朋友玛丽·艾伦介绍给他
and I fixed him up with my friend Mary Ellen...
玛丽·艾伦今晚没有来  因为她...
...who couldn't be here tonight, because.... It's not--
这不重要  她在戒毒...
It's not important. Well, she's in rehab.
总之呢
Anyway.
乔伊说他要介绍他的朋友迈克给我认识
So Joey said that he was fixing me up with his friend Mike...
但他并不认识什么叫迈克的朋友
...only he didn't have a friend Mike,
所以他呢  就把我的迈克带去了
so he just brought my Mike.
然后...
And-- And--
尽管如此... 呃  结果呢  结果还不错
But despite, you know-- It got good.
好  我想抽一点点时间来
Ok, I wanna take a moment
缅怀下我妈妈
to mention my mother,
她今晚不能出席  因为...
who couldn't be here.
哦  天呐
Oh, God.
呃...缅怀时间结束
And.... And moment's over.
好的  不  这个就不说了
So okay.... Oh, no, forget that.
这个也不说了  这个很有意思
I can forget that. Oh, this is funny.
哦  但首先你得知道...
Oh, but you need to know that to get that.
所以   好吧  我...
So.... Oh, well, okay.
我...
I.... Okay.
好了  莫妮卡  我再也受不了了
Okay, Monica, I can't do it like this!
这是我的婚礼  知道吗
This is my wedding, okay?
我不需要这样
I don't want this--
或者这样  或者这样
Or this-- Or this--
好吗  我要的只是一个简单的婚礼
Okay? I just wanted a simple wedding...
我要我的未婚夫能够
...where my fiance can go to the bathroom
随心所欲地上厕所
any time he wants!
-你知道吗  你别干了   -什么
- You know what? You're done. - What?
你被炒了
You're fired!
干杯
Cheers.
-嘿   -新婚快乐
- Hey. - Happy wedding day.
也祝你快乐
Happy my wedding day to you.
好了  乔伊   听着
Joey, listen,
从现在开始  这里是伴娘的地盘
this is gonna be bridesmaid central,
明白了吗
all right?
我们要在卫生间里面做头发
We're gonna have hair and makeup
化妆
in the bathroom.
我要把冰箱里的东西挪一下
I had to move a couple things in the fridge
给襟花出地方
to make room for the corsages.
真是的  早知道有襟花
Man! I wouldn't have had breakfast
我就不吃早饭了
if I knew there was gonna be corsages.
嗨
Hi.
昨晚...
About last night....
我知道你压力很大  所以...
I know you're under a lot of stress, and....
尽管你说的话
Well, even though the things you said
让我有点伤心
...as someone who's never been fired before--
我的意思是...
My point is....
好吧  我愿意复职
Well, I'm willing to take my job back.
哦  还是算了吧
Oh, well, that's okay.
我觉得如果你只做伴娘的话
I think you and I will do much better
情况会好得多
if you're just here as a bridesmaid.
既然你这么说
Is that so?
好吧
Okay.
如果你真这么想的话
If that's really what you want,
那给你
then here.
给你这个耳机
I give you the headset.
我还是不太想给你这个耳机
I don't really wanna give you the headset.
还有就是  如果你要接手的话
I guess if you're taking over,
你大概需要回复这些信息
then you should probably return these messages.
哇  真不少啊
Wow. This is a lot.
我相信你能处理它们
But I'm sure you can handle this.
我是说  尽管
I have won awards...
我曾经获得过组织技能奖
...for my organizational skills.
但是呢  我相信你肯定没问题
But I'm sure you'll do fine.
你获过奖
You've won awards?
是我用自己的电脑打印出来的.
I printed them out on my computer.
-嘿  -嗨
- Hey. - Hi.
瑞秋呢
Where's Rach?
她在自己的房间  有事吗
She's in her room. Why?
我要跟她谈谈
I have to talk to her about
关于那个伴郎的问题
this groomsman situation.
我可不想像个傻子一样坐在那儿
Ok, I'm not gonna watch Chandler up there
看着钱德勒在婚礼上露脸
while I'm in the seats like some chump.
天呐  你简直美翻了
My God, you're breathtaking.
你想干嘛
What do you want?
你还没决定
You haven't by any chance
伴郎的人选吧
chosen a groomsman yet, have you?
罗斯
Ross,
我已经很为难了  你就别再添乱了
please don't make this harder than it already is.
我没有啊
I'm not.
我是在让事情简单化  选我
I'm making it easier. Pick me.
钱德勒也说这个机会对他十分重要
Chandler said it's important to him too.
听着  听着
Listen. Listen.
无论你选谁
Whoever you pick
他可是要跟你一起走过红地毯
is gonna walk down the aisle with you.
我可以保证  到时候我一个字也不会说
Now, I promise I won't say a word.
但如果你选钱德勒的话
But if you pick Chandler...
他肯定会一直在你耳朵旁边嘀咕他那些
...he's gonna be whispering stupid jokes
无聊的玩笑
in your ear the whole time.
哦...  你确实强一点
Oh, you are the lesser of two evils.
没错
Yes!
塞文  我不知道你在说什么
Sven, I don't understand what you're saying.
花又有什么问题了
What is wrong with the flowers?
罗肯斯  "罗肯斯"是什么鬼东西
"Lorkins"? What the hell are "lorkins"?
我知道
I know.
嘿
Hey.
嘿  迈克  如果你是瑞典人
Mike, if you were Swedish...
你说"罗肯斯"  那会是哪种花
...and you were saying the word "lorkins," what flower would that be?
兰花
Orchids?
就是这个
Right there!
这就是我嫁给你的原因
That's why I'm marrying you.
你好  迈克尔
Hello, Michael.
乔瑟夫
Joseph.
我能跟你说两句吗
May I have a word with you, please?
这里真是...
This is...
棒极了
...great.
坐
Have a seat.
昨天晚上
Last night...
我试着欢迎你进入我们的家族
...l tried to welcome you into my family.
然而  你对我很不尊重
And instead, you disrespect me.
我不能容忍这一点
I cannot allow this.
你是在排演什么劣制黑手党电影吗
Are you rehearsing for some really bad Mafia movie?
还敢顶嘴
More back talk.
没错
And yes,
我是借用了几句
I may be borrowing a few lines
我最近试镜的剧集
from my recent unsuccessful audition...
《家族荣耀 II》
...for Family Honor 2:
《就是今天  这是私事》里几句台词
This A-Time It's A-Personal.
乔伊  我今天比较忙
Joey, I kind of have a lot to do today.
你到底想要干嘛
What do you want?
我想要你认真一点
I want you to take this seriously!
菲比对我来说非常
Phoebe is very,
非常的重要  知道吗
very important to me, okay?
我要你保证
I wanna make sure
你会好好照顾她
you are gonna take care of her.
乔伊  我爱菲比
Joe, I love Phoebe.
在我的生命中没有什么比她更重要
She's the most important thing in my life.
我宁死也不会让她受到任何伤害
I'd die before I let anything happen to her.
这才是我想听的
That's what I wanted to hear.
因为我当她是家人  知道吗
Because she's family, okay?
现在你也要成为家里的一份子了
And now you're gonna be family.
在世界上没有什么事
And there's nothing more important
比家庭更重要
in the whole world than family.
那个电影可真是烂得可以
That must have been one lousy movie.
这不是台词  是我说的
That was me!
嘿
Hi.
我能跟你商量一下伴郎的事吗
Let's talk about this groomsman thing.
如果你选罗斯
If you pick Ross,
你们俩只能安安静静地走过红地毯
he'll walk you down the aisle just fine.
但如果你选我的话
But if you choose me...
你可就有乐子听了
...you'll be getting some comedy.
即便如此...
Even so...
我想我还是得选罗斯
...l think I'm gonna pick Ross.
我来告诉你为什么你要选我
Let me tell you why you need to pick me.
当我还是个孩子的时候
See, when I was a kid, you know,
无论做什么  我总是被冷落的那个
I was always left out of everything...
你知道 这种经历总是让我缺乏安全感
You know... and it really made me feel insecure.
在运动场上我永远都是被人家挑剩下的那个
I was always picked last in gym...
甚至在那个胖子交换生后面
...even behind that fat exchange student
他甚至都不知道棒球的规则
who didn't know the rules to baseball.
那个家伙三击不中
I mean, this guy would strike out
还撂下球棒就朝三垒上跑
and then run to third.
总之  如果我成为唯一一个
Anyway, if I'm the only one
不能参加婚礼的人
left out of this wedding...
以前那些凄惨的回忆
...l just know that all those feelings
就会再次浮现在眼前
are gonna come rushing back.
好吧  我选你
All right, fine, I pick you.
太棒了
Yes!
终于有钱德勒的一席之地了
Make "groom" for Chandler.
噢  我的天
Oh, my.
不  要照我说的做
No, we're gonna do it my way.
因为你的办法太白痴了
Because your way is stupid.
好了  我要挂了
All right, I got to go.
有电话正打进来  牧师
I have another call, Reverend.
喂
Hello?
很高兴能跟你聊聊
I'm glad we had this little talk.
是啊
Yes.
也谢谢你关于洞房的那些建议
And thanks for all the wedding night advice.
我一点都不觉得尴尬
That didn't make me uncomfortable at all.
好了  就这样吧  大家晚上见喽
All right, so I'll see everybody tonight.
-好  -再见
- Okay. - Bye.
你们知道
Did you guys know that
在走廊里有个大号的冰雕么
there's a giant ice sculpture in the hall?
我的天  这怎么回事啊
Oh, my God, what's it doing here?
我猜是送货的家伙把投递地址
I guess it got sent to the billing address
和付款人地址搞混了
as opposed to the shipping address.
这下麻烦了
What a pickle.
我的天啊   什么事都是一团糟
Oh, my God, everything's such a mess.
为什么这些事情会发生在我身上
Why is this happening to me?
你们想不想用舌头去舔舔它
How bad do you wanna stick your tongue on that?
-你怎么样  -我很好啊
- How's it going? - Good.
我来要点咖啡喝
I'm just getting some coffee
这样我能在婚礼上清醒一点
so I'm alert for the wedding.
我也是这么打算的
That's what I was doing too.
那好  今晚玩得高兴点
Well, you have fun tonight.
-你也是  -哦  我会的
- You too. - Oh, I will.
我也会的
Me too.
慢着
Wait a minute.
我知道自己为什么这么得意
I know why I'm being such an ass.
但你为什么也这样
Why are you?
我不能告诉你
I'm not supposed to tell you.
你同时答应我们两个人参加仪式
You told us both we could be in the wedding?
我的解释是
In my defense,
你们不应该告诉对方的
you weren't supposed to tell each other!
瑞秋  只有一个人可以参加婚礼仪式
Rachel, only one of us can do it.
你必须要选一个
You have to choose.
你和我  在一起...
You and me together again.
瑞秋  瑞秋
Rach, Rach?
咚  咚
Knock-knock.
-是谁啊  -在婚礼上我再告诉你
- Who's there? - I'll tell you at the wedding.
嘿  我忘了围巾了
Hey, I forgot my scarf.
我做不来
You know what. I can't do this.
我真的不知道应该选谁
I don't know which one of you guys to pick.
哦  你还没选好呢
Oh, you haven't picked yet?
太好了  我有个好主意
Oh, good, because I had an idea.
我觉得如果由我们家的狗
I thought it would be fun
恰皮来担任伴郎的话肯定很有意思
if the third groomsman was my family dog, Chappy.
什么  一只狗
What? A dog?
不  让瑞秋来选
No. Rachel gets to choose.
真是难以抉择啊
Wow, this is a tough one.
看起来我只有选那只狗了
I think I'm gonna have to go with the dog.
等一下  你是说
So, what you're saying is that
厨子已经到汉密尔顿俱乐部了
the chef is at the Hamilton Club...
但食物还没有送到
...but the food is not?
饮料和酒水已经送到了
And the drinks are there
但男招待还没有到
but the bartender is not?
你...他妈的开什么玩笑
Are you freaking kidding me?
怎么样了
How's it going?
-帮帮我...  -什么
- Help me. - What?
我想让你做回疯婆子了
I want you to be crazy bitch again.
真的
Really?
求你了
Please?
你真想让我回来
You really want me to come back?
胜过我想结婚
More than I wanna get married.
好  伙计们  我又回来了
Okay, people, we are back in business!
天呐  我可想死你了
Oh, God, I have missed you so much. Okay.
好了  去做头发化妆吧
Ok. Get your hair and makeup done.
这儿一切交给我好了
I'll take care of everything.
嘿  你们打算怎么办
Hey, what are you guys gonna do?
什么怎么办
About what?
暴风雪啊  我刚看新闻
The blizzard. I just saw on the news...
说这是20年来最大的一场暴风雪
...it's the worst snowstorm in 20 years.
所有的桥和隧道都关闭了
They already closed all the bridges and tunnels.
可是乐队和摄像师
But the band and the photographer
还要从新泽西赶过来呢
are coming in from New Jersey.
看来来不了了
I don't think they are.
嘿嘿  看起来你恐怕
Looks like you're not gonna
也参加不了仪式了吧
be in the wedding, either.
真遗憾啊  菲比
So sorry, Pheebs.
俱乐部停电了
Well, the club lost its power.
是啊  听新闻说  市里大部分地区都停电了
Yeah according to the news, most of the city did.
你从什么时候开始看起新闻来了
Since when do you watch the news?
告诉你好了
For your information...
从那个靓女开始主持天气预报的时候
...since they hired a very hot weather girl.
真不敢相信
I can't believe
你们两个今天的婚礼办不成了
you aren't getting married today.
是啊
I know.
哇  你们看  外面真的好美
Wow, you know, it's so beautiful out there.
你们不是总想在户外举行婚礼吗
You always wanted to get married outside.
你们俩干嘛不干脆在街上结婚呢
Why don't you just do it on the street?
什么
What?
看  雪几乎已经停了
Well, look, it's hardly snowing anymore.
我是说  没有比这更加浪漫的布景了
I mean, you couldn't ask for a more romantic setting.
这不正是你一直想要的
This could be the simple wedding
简单的婚礼吗
you've always wanted.
你认为呢
What do you think?
我只想今天就跟你结婚
I think I wanna get married to you today.
我也是  莫妮卡  你觉得这样可行吗
Me too. Monica, do you think we could do it?
赞成
Affirmative!
好   大家把椅子都搬出来
Okay, let's get these chairs out here!
甘瑟  把圣诞用的灯饰都打亮
Gunther, hit the Christmas lights.
喂   是哪个家伙把冰雕放在
Okay, who left the ice sculpture
热水井旁边的
on the steam grate?
迈克
Michael.
嘿  你们到了  太棒了  恰皮
Hey, you made it. Great. Chappy!
-对啊  -嗨
- There you go. - Hi. Hi.
妈妈  我知道在大街上结婚这种事
Mom, I know getting married in the street isn't
肯定不合你的脾气
what you approve of.
不  这挺有趣儿的
No, it's lovely.
又是灯又是雪的
The lights and the snow.
我怎么看都看不够
I could look at them forever.
我刚才在她的饮料里下了点药
I crushed a pill and put it in her drink.
来吧  亲爱的
Come on, sweetheart.
恰皮太弱小了
You know, Chappy's too small
它恐怕难以应付这一地的积雪
to handle all this snow.
到时候需要有人抱着它走过红毯
Someone has to walk him down the aisle.
那么  这个人也算参加了婚礼仪式吧
Would this person be in the wedding?
我想是吧.
I guess.
-我来  -我来
- I'll do it! - I'll do it!
等等  钱德勒
Chandler, hello?
你不是害怕狗吗
I mean, aren't you scared of dogs?
谁说我害怕
I'm not scared.
我只要抱着小恰皮 然后...
I'll just take little Chappy and--
它知道我害怕它
He can sense my fear!
我喘不上气来了
My throat is exposed!
我想  出现在婚礼上的人就是我喽
I guess I'm in the wedding then.
它好臭
He stinks.
一级警报
Level one alert!
重复  一级警报  这不是演习
I repeat, level one, this is not a drill!
我们碰到难题了
We have a situation.
牧师刚才打电话来说
The minister called.
他被大雪困住  赶不过来了
He's snowed in, he can't make it.
-哦  不是吧  -嘿  甭担心
- Oh, no. - Hey, don't worry.
你们结婚  我获得的牧师资格到现在还有效
I'm still ordained from your wedding.
真的
Really?
是啊  你认为我会放弃牧师资格吗
Yeah. You think I'd give up being a minister
那样的话我坐地铁就不能免票了
and pay to ride the subway?
牧师坐地铁不免费的
Ministers don't ride the subway for free.
我仔细研究过圣经的
I had to read the Bible pretty carefully,
没错  我们不用买票
but, yeah, we do.
好的  如果让乔伊来主持婚礼的话
Ok, if Joey does the ceremony,
那我们还需要有个人来挽着菲比
then we have to find someone else to walk Phoebe down the aisle.
我来
I'll do it!
好  迈克和乔伊  各就各位
Okay, Mike and Joey, get in position.
钱德勒  跟我来
Chandler, come with me.
乔伊负责主持婚礼
Okay, Joey's doing the ceremony,
你由钱德勒负责
and Chandler's giving you away.
哦  好  嗨  新爹
Oh, okay. Hi, new Dad.
那么  你准备好了么
So you ready to do this?
天呐  这一切都是真的
Oh, my God. This is really happening.
菲比  我真替你高兴  亲爱的
Phoebe, I'm so happy for you, honey.
谢谢
Thank you.
我爱你   等等
I love you. Wait, wait!
不要抱  当心礼服
No hugs! The dresses!
管它的
Oh, what the hell.
来吧
Oh, come on.
我爱你们
I love you guys.
我爱你
I love you.
好了  关键时刻到了
Okay, it's zero hour!
各小组听我的指令行事
All teams execute on my count!
我们开始吧
Let's get this bad boy on the road!
我想让你今晚戴着这副耳机上床  你不反对吧
Is it okay I want you to wear that headset in bed?
根据计划  裸体时间被安排在23:00
I have you scheduled for nudity at 2300 hours.
噢耶
Oh, yeah.
好了  马乔里  开始敲你的吧
Okay, Marjorie, hit it.
天呐  罗斯  你就不能先洗个澡吗
Jeez, Ross. You could've showered.
是狗身上的味
It's the dog.
伴郎  为什么只有你一个人站在这儿
Groomsman? Why are you standing there?
你的伴娘呢
Where's your bridesmaid?
我们遇到情况了
We've got a broken arrow!
伴娘失踪了
Bridesmaid down!
噢  是我自己
Oh, that's me.
-准备好了么  -好了
- Ready? - Okay.
哦  等一下  哦  等等
Oh, wait. Oh, no. Wait.
哇  不会冷吗
Wow. Aren't you gonna be cold?
我不在乎
I don't care.
我要做自己的"蓝色物"
I'll be my "something blue."
-你看起来美极了  -谢谢
- You look beautiful. - Thank you.
天呐
My God.
你不冷吗
Aren't you freezing?
朋友们  家人们
Friends. Family.
狗儿
Dog.
感谢你们能够到场来
Thank you all for being here
见证这一场天赐的姻缘
to witness this blessed event.
冷空气已经蔓延到
The cold has now spread
我"那里"了
to my special place...
所以我会长话短说
...so I'm gonna do the short version of this.
菲比和迈克是完美的一对儿
Phoebe and Mike are perfect for each other.
我相信在场的每一个人都会和我一样
And I know I speak for everyone here...
祝愿他们一生幸福
...when I wish them a lifetime of happiness.
戒指呢
Who has the rings?
好的
Okay.
在我成长的过程中
When I was growing up,
我不曾拥有真正的父爱和母爱
I didn't have a normal mom and dad...
或者和别人一样拥有一个正常的家庭
...or a regular family like everybody else.
我一直知道自己缺少些什么
And I always knew that something was missing.
然而现在  我站在这里
But now I'm standing here today...
我知道自己已经得到了
...knowing that I have everything
自己所需要的一切
I'm ever gonna need.
你就是我的家人
You are my family.
菲比  你是这么的美丽
Phoebe, you are so beautiful.
这么的善良  这么的大方
You're so kind. You're so generous.
古怪的你是那么的迷人
You're so wonderfully weird.
和你在一起的每一天都像是一次探险
Every day with you is an adventure.
我简直不敢相信自己是如此地幸运
And I can't believe how lucky I am.
我迫不急待地想要和你
And I can't wait to
分享自己的生命历程  直到永远
share my life with you forever.
等一下  我忘了说
Oh, wait! Oh, I forgot. And...
我爱你
...l love you.
还有  你的眼睛很漂亮
And you have nice eyes.
我也爱你
I love you too.
-乔伊  -怎么了
- Joey? - Yeah?
恰皮的心脏非常慢了
Chappy's heart rate has slowed way down.
好的  菲比
Okay. Phoebe...
你愿意让这个男人成为你的丈夫吗
...do you take this man to be your husband?
我愿意
I do.
迈克  你愿意让这个女人成为你的妻子吗
Mike, do you take this woman to be your wife?
我愿意
I do.
我现在正式宣布
I now pronounce you...
你们结为夫妻
...husband and wife.
我结婚了
I got married!
谁递给我件衣服
Could someone get me a coat?
我快要冻僵了
I'm frigging freezing.
这婚礼太赞了
It really was an incredible wedding.
是啊
It was.
我真不想让它就那么结束  嘿
I kind of don't want it to end. Hey...
你想来喝一杯吗
...you wanna come in for a drink
然后来一口襟花
and a bite of corsage?
我很想去  但现在已经23:00了
I'd love to, but it's 2300 hours...
我现在要去
...and I'm about to have the most organized sex
经历一次有史以来最有组织的性爱
anyone's ever had.
嘿  罗斯呢
Whatever happened to Ross?
我不知道
I don't know.
刚才他还在跟一个辣妹聊天来着
Maybe he hooked up with
大概两个人搞在一起了吧
that hot girl he talked to.
快点  恰皮  拜托你快点解决了吧,
Come on, Chappy! Do your business!
拉啊
Make!
我参加婚礼可不是为了做这个
I did not sign on for this.